初次翻译字幕，如有漏误，请多多包涵指正。@塔拉Tala
It scares us just thinking about it.
一想到它就让我们觉得很害怕.
它都快把我们逼疯了
When you hear it, you're gonna
think we're insane.
麻烦你再重新讲一遍，从头开始。
Try us. Please, from the start.
其实开始的时候并不是很严重，比如它的手或者腿的位置会移动。
It started out small,
like a hand or a leg was in a different position.
后来，它的头会突然抬起来
Then its head was looking up
instead of down.
再后来，有一天，我们发现它自己跑到了另外的房间里。
And then one day, it was in
a completely different room.
It was moving around by itself.
有没有想过也许有其他人会有你们公寓的钥匙，可能这只是个恶作剧？
Ever think maybe somebody had a key
to your apartment and was playing a trick?
我们以前有这么想过
That's exactly what we thought.
但是我们从未发现过有任何人进来的迹象。
But never once did we find any
sign or evidence of intrusion.
所以，你们认为你们的布偶被附身了？
And this all led you to believe
that the doll was possessed?
是的
Yes.
Camilla 之前联系过一个灵媒，她说有一位名叫
Camilla got in touch with a medium.
We learned from her that a 7-year-old girl...
Annabelle Higgins的7岁女孩曾经死在这座公寓里。
...named Annabelle Higgins
had died in this apartment.
她很孤独，而且她很喜欢我们的布偶。
She was lonely and took a liking
to my doll.
她只是需要朋友
All she wanted was to be friends.
听到这些之后，我们觉得很难过
When we heard this,
we felt really sorry for her.
我的意思是说，我们是护士，我们可以帮助别人。
I mean, we're nurses, we help people.
所以。。。
So...
我们决定让她搬到玩偶里
...we gave her permission
to move into the doll.
等等，你们做了什么?
Wait, you did what?
她想在玩偶里栖身，所以她就可以和我们住在一起。
She wanted to live with us
by inhabiting the doll.
所以我们同意了。
We said yes.
可是，接下来，事情变得更糟糕了。
But then things got worse.
天哪。。。
God.
当我们回到公寓的时候，她坐在走廊的地板上。
When we came home,
she was sitting in the hallway.
可实际上，我们一直让她待在客房里。
But we had left her in the spare room.
等一下，Debbie。
Debbie! Debbie, wait!
我们害怕极了。
We are beyond terrified.
我们不知道发生了什么事，也不知道应该怎么办，你能帮助我们吗?
We don't know what's going on
or what to do. Can you help us?
当然。
Yes, we can.
现在，你们听着，首先，事情并不是像你们以为的那样是鬼魂附身什么的
Now, firstly, there's no such thing
as Annabelle, and there never was.
而且鬼魂也不具备这样的能力。
Ghosts don't possess such power.
我想所有的这一切都是有什么东西在背后操纵。
I think what we have here is something
extremely manipulative.
一种非人类的东西。
It's something inhuman.
最大的问题是你们不应该理会这个玩偶。
It was a big mistake acknowledging this doll.
也正因为如此，你们才会上当。
And through that,
the inhuman spirit tricked you.
才会扰乱你们的生活。
You gave it permission
to infest your lives.
你指的是什么？
What's an inhuman spirit?
一种不可能和人类共生的东西。
It's something that's never walked
the earth in human form.
一种很邪恶的东西。
It's something demonic.
所以，你是说，并不是玩偶被鬼魂附身了？
So the doll was never possessed?
对，它只是一个被用来传递信息的载体。
No, no, it was used as a conduit.
It was moved around to give
the impression of possession.
恶灵不会控制物体，它只会控制人。
Demonic spirits don't possess things,
they possess people.
它真正想要的是控制你们。
It wanted to get inside of you.
好了，Drew，这很不错，你可以把那个关掉了。
All right, that's good, Drew.
You can shut it down now.
开一下灯。
Hit the lights.
后来，我们让教会委派一位神父过去保护那座房子和住户。
So we got the church to send a priest over...
...to bless the house and the occupants.
不管那个公寓里究竟有什么，但现在已经没事了。还有什么问题吗？
Whatever was oppressing that apartment
was no longer with them. Any questions?
左边的那位
Yes.
那个玩偶现在在哪里？
Where's the doll now?
在一个安全的地方
Someplace safe.
那一位。
那么，你们算什么？
- Yep.
- So, what are you guys?
我是说，别人怎么称呼你们这种人？
I mean, what do people call you?
哦，这个嘛，人们会叫我们驱魔师。
Uh, well, we've been called Demonologists.
That's one name for us.
或者捉鬼人、超自然现象研究者。
Ghost hunters, paranormal researchers.
怪物。哈哈～
- Kooks.
- Ha-ha-ha.
疯子
Wackos.
但是我们更喜欢别人叫我们Ed 和 Lorraine Warren
But we prefer to be known simply
as Ed and Lorraine Warren.
我们到了。
Here we are.
哇，你听到了吗？
Wow, hear that?
我什么都没听到。
- I don't hear anything.
- Exactly.
呵呵
Oh. Ha!
好了，伙计们，我们到了，都下车吧。
- Okay. Guys, we are here!
- Get out of the car.
天哪，这里真是前不着村后不着店。
Oh, God, we're in the middle of nowhere.
很兴奋，对不对？
是的。
Are you so excited?
Where's my "yes"? Where's my "yes"? Yes!
我们来赛跑吧
I'll race you!
你们是不是觉得很兴奋？
是的。
- Are you guys excited?
- Yes!
我太激动了！
快点儿，Sadie
- I'm so excited!
- Come on, Sadie!
我要住自己的房间。
I get my own room!
你开玩笑吧？你可没有优先权。
Are you kidding me?
No dibs on the rooms!
什么？
- What?
我可以挑选我自己的房间吗？
还是说我没有选择？
So do I get to pick my own room?
Or do I have no choice in that either?
唉～一旦她遇到一个可爱的男孩子时，她就会忘了Jersey
Well, first cute boy she meets,
she'll forget about Jersey.
那很好。
我希望是吧。
- Great.
- I hope.
我都等不及了。
I can't wait.
过来，Sadie。
Come on, Sadie.
Sadie，我们进去吧。
Sadie, let's go.
嘿～快点
Hey, come.
你怎么了？
What's the matter with you?
嘿，快点儿。
Hey, come on, girl.
好吧，你自便吧。
All right, suit yourself.
你叫什么名字？
- What's your name?
你的爸爸是谁？
- Who's your daddy?
他很富有吗？
是不是像我一样富有？
- He rich?
- Is he rich like me?
看着脚下
Watch your step.
借过借过
Coming through.
小心点儿，爸爸
Whoa, watch out, Dad.
你想把它放在哪儿？
客厅
- Where do you want it?
- In the living room.
Andrea，我的风铃在哪里？
我想Nancy把它放到其他房间了。
- Andrea, where's my wind chime?
- I think Nancy's got it in the other room.
谢谢。Nancy，你见过我的风铃吗？
Thanks. Hey, Nancy,
have you seen my wind chime?
这个吗？
对，谢谢
- Oh, this one?
- Yeah, thanks.
你必须要接住它。
Nancy，放手，把它给我。
- You're gonna have to catch it.
- Nancy! Let go! Give it here.
你真讨厌。
You're so mean.
妈妈，我可以把我的风铃挂起来吗？
Hey, Mom, can I hang up
my wind chime?
当然，你可以挂在外边的绳子上。
Of course. There's a line outside
you can hang it on.
宝贝，把April带进屋，好吗？天就快要黑了。
Honey, have April come in, okay?
It's gonna be dark soon.
好
Okay.
快点，April ，妈妈让我们进去。
Come on, April! Mom wants us inside!
Cindy，看看我找到了什么。
Look what I found, Cindy.
One...
...two...
...three.
不许偷看
Come on, come on, come on.
No peeking.
Four.
你们可以把披萨都吃完吗？不要浪费。
Are you guys done with the pizza?
I don't want it going to waste.
我们走
养活你们这些女孩儿可真难。
- Let's go.
- It's expensive feeding you girls.
7，8，9，10
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
我应该藏在哪里？
Where should I hide?
准备好了吗？我要来了。。
Ready or not, here I come!
好，拍拍手。
Okay, clap.
哇
你还不熟悉这个房子。
- Whoa!
- You don't know the house well enough.
有人会受伤的。
Someone's gonna get hurt.
我没事。
I'm okay, I'm okay.
第二次拍手
Second clap.
那是作弊
That's cheating.
拍手
Clap.
抓到你了
哈哈
- Got you!
- Aah!
你还好吗？
嗯
- Are you okay? Um--
- Yeah.
打碎什么了？
All right, what did we break now?
我不是故意的
离开这里。
- I didn't mean to.
- Move out of there, please.
是Christine的错
It was Christine's fault.
我的错？天。。
- Oh, jeez.
- My fault? Oh, my God.
都是Christine搞的
不，我没有
- Christine did it.
- No, I didn't.
是你推我的
才不是，是你跌倒了。
- You pushed me.
- No, no, you fell back.
Nancy，你可以去帮我把火柴拿来吗？
Hey, Nancy, can you go get me
the matches, please?
发生什么事情了？
What's going on?
Nancy把东西打破了
闭嘴
- Nancy broke something.
- Shut up.
什么破了？
墙
- What broke?
- It's the wall.
哇哦
我想我们有一个地窖或者什么东东
- Whoa.
- I think we have a cellar or something.
我想看看，走开走开
I wanna see, I wanna see. Move, move, move.
火柴来了。谢谢你
Here, matches. Thank you.
我想要看看
你可以看
- I wanna see.
- You can see.
我想看看
你们都可以看
- I wanna see.
- You can all see.
Move!
噢，天哪
Oh, man.
Huh.
Roger？
Roger?
下面有什么？
What do you see down there?
很难描述。
Just, uh, hard to tell, you know?
一架老式钢琴，还有一大堆垃圾
It's an old piano
and a whole bunch of garbage.
妈的
Agh. Son of a--
哇～
Wow.
Rog?
快上来
Come on up.
你们女孩子不许下去那里。
I don't want you girls going down there.
那个地方到处都是蜘蛛。
- That place is loaded with spiders.
- Ew!
别紧张
Just relax. Okay.
别闹了Nancy，那不好玩。
Stop it, Nancy. It's not funny.
总之，现在我们多了一些额外的空间。。明天早晨我会去查看一下。
We've got extra square footage anyway.
I'll check it out in the morning.
我想知道为什么那里被木板封起来了
我不知道
- I wonder why it was boarded up.
- I don't know.
好了，演出结束了。
Okay, show's over.
再让我们玩5分钟吧
不行
- Five minutes.
- No more minutes.
上床
马上上床睡觉
- Up to bed. Please. Thank you.
- Right to bed.
我快累死了
Man, I'm fried.
Sadie好像很烦躁
Something's up with Sadie.
嗯，我不知道是怎么回事
它死活不肯进门
Yeah, I don't know what her problem is.
Couldn't get her to come inside.
我们不能让她呆在外边
We can't leave her out there.
没事，我给她拴上链子了。
She's all right. I got her on a chain.
Sadie，安静点儿
Sadie, hey, be quiet.
谢谢你让所做的一切。
Thanks for making this work.
我知道你为此付出了很多
I know it was a lot to bite off.
一切都会好的，对吗？
It's gonna be great, isn't it?
我觉得已经很棒了
I think it's great already.
是的
Yeah.
你是不是累得都不能为咱们的新房子来一次“洗礼仪式”了？
You still too fried to christen
the new house?
谁说我累了？
Who said I'm fried?
咱这儿没人觉得累吗？
哈哈
- Ain't nobody here's fried.
- Ha, ha.
妈妈
Mom?
嗨，你们睡得怎么样？
Hey. How did you guys sleep?
好冷呀
I'm cold.
这里的确有点儿冷
It is chilly, isn't it?
难道我们就不能买一座有马桶的房子吗？
You think maybe we could have bought
a house with a toilet that actually works?
去跟你爸爸说吧
Tell your father.
昨天晚上我都房间里有一股特别臭的味道，就像有什么东西死了。
And there was a funky smell in my
room last night. Like something died.
现在还有吗？
没了
- Is it still there?
- No.
那就没事了
Problem solved.
Roger?
在下面，亲爱的。
Down here, honey.
早
Morning.
哇哦
Ooh. Whoa.
要清理这里可是要费点儿功夫。
This is gonna take some
serious elbow grease.
是呀
Yeah.
噢天哪
Oh, my God.
我们要如何处理这些东东
What are we gonna do
with all this stuff?
我们可能应该就把它们全部丢掉
Well, we probably ought
to go through it, you know?
这里备不住藏着什么值钱的古董吧？
There might be some antiques down here
worth a lot.
也备不住就只是一堆垃圾，连前任房主都不想要。
Yeah, or just a lot of junk
the previous owner didn't want.
总之，现在都是我们的了。
嗯，都是咱的了
- It's ours now.
- Knock yourself out.
我去弄点儿咖啡
好
- I'm gonna make some coffee.
- Okay.
我要看看这个火炉还能不能用
I'm gonna see if I can get
this furnace working.
那太好了，这里冷得跟冰窖一样。
Yeah, that'd be nice. It's freezing.
嗯
Yeah.
HUM
Sadie，出来
Sadie! Come here, Sadie!
妈妈
Mommy!
妈妈，Sadie在哪儿
Mommy, where's Sadie?
她在外边。她肯定很饿了，你去把她牵进来吧
She's outside. You know, I'm sure she's
hungry by now. Why don't you go and get her.
哇哦
早上好，爸爸
- Whoa.
- Morning, Dad.
你能帮我拿着这个吗
嗯
- Can you hold this?
- Sure.
Sadie
慢一点，Scoot
- Sadie!
- Slow it down, Scoot.
- Roger.
嗯？
- Yeah.
这个钟停在了3：07，走廊里的那个也一样。
This clock stopped at 3:07,
and so did the one in the hallway.
那很古怪。
That's weird.
可能坏了吧
Maybe it got knocked around in the move.
说到这个，顺便问一下，你对我的腿做了什么？
Speaking of knocked around,
what did you do to me last night?
噢～我没有做什么呀，那是我弄得吗？
我不知道
- Ouch. I didn't do that. Did l?
- I don't know.
Sadie
Sadie!
April， April
April! April!
April，你怎么了？
What's--? April! What's going on?
发生什么事了
噢天哪
- What happened?
- Oh, my God!
噢～Sadie
Oh, Sadie.
我们把所有的东东都锁在这里
We keep everything locked in here.
你随便看看吧
Feel free to look around.
但是什么都别碰
Just don't touch anything.
哇
Wow.
这简直太疯狂了
This is crazy.
那么，所有的这些玩意儿都来自你所调查过的那些案子？
So all these are taken from cases
you've investigated?
对，你所看到的所有的东东都是被恶灵附体的，被诅咒过的，
That's right. Everything you see
in here is either haunted, cursed...
或者是被用来举行某种仪式的
...or has been used in some kind
of ritualistic practice.
连玩具也是？
Nothing's a toy.
甚至就连那个玩具猴子也一样
Not even the toy monkey.
别碰～！
Don't touch it.
那，这些东东都放在你的房间里你不觉得害怕吗？或者担忧？
Oh, ahem. Well, isn't it scary,
or doesn't it worry you...
或者担忧？
...to have all these items
right in your home?
这就是为什么每个月神父都会来这里的原因。
That's why we have a priest that comes by
once a month to bless the room.
我对此的看法是，
Well, the way I see it is:
它们待在这座房子里要远远比待在外边更安全。
It's safer for these things
to be in here than out there.
这和要让枪支远离街头的道理的一样的。
It's kind of like keeping guns
off the street.
为什么不直接把它们扔进焚化炉里烧毁它们？
Why not just throw them
in an incinerator? Destroy them.
那没什么用，能烧毁的仅仅是这些被利用的物体而已。
Well, that would only destroy the vessel.
有时候，最好的办法是把鬼啊妖怪什么的封在瓶子里。
Sometimes it's better to keep
the genie in the bottle.
玩偶Annabelle是不是也在这里？
Say, is the, uh, Annabelle doll here?
就在这边。
Right this way.
嗯
Yeah.
你说过她只是一个载体？
对
- You said she's a conduit?
- That's right.
那指的是什么意思？
What does that mean?
她被有一个力量非常强大的恶灵侵占了
A very powerful demonic
has latched itself onto her.
你们就是研究类似恶灵缠身这类事情的？
So when you guys investigate
these hauntings...
你如何来避免它们接近你？
...how do you stop them
from latching onto you?
我们必须要高度警惕
We have to take great precaution.
那，你的妻子呢？
But what about your wife?
她怎么了？
What about her?
神父Gordon告诉过我。
Well, Father Gordon told me that--
噢，那不一样。
Well, that was different.
我妻子是在驱魔的时候出事的
What happened to my wife
happened during an exorcism.
那有什么不同？
Well, what's the difference?
抱歉
Excuse me.
宝贝，你在干什么？
Honey, what are you doing?
过来这里
Come here.
你很清楚你不该来这里，对吗？
You know better. All right?
Georgiana?
过来～！你有没有碰过什么东西？
没有
- Come on. Did you touch anything?
- No.
好吧，过来宝贝
All right, come on, honey.
Georgiana，你能带Judy上楼吗？
好的
- Georgiana! Could you take Judy upstairs?
- Oh, sure.
不管怎么样，你都不可以进这个房间，记住了吗?
You can't go into this room,
no matter what, remember?
知道了爸爸
好
- Yes, Daddy.
- All right.
去吧
好，过来
- Go on.
- Okay, come on.
我来给你找点儿吃的，好吗？走吧
Let's see if I can find you
a little snack, okay? Come on.
这里发生什么事了？
Hey. What's going on in here?
爸爸，你看
你看起来真漂亮
- Daddy, look.
- You look very pretty.
弄好了。
去穿好衣服，该吃晚饭了。
All right, all done.
Go get dressed for dinner.
我要穿着这个吃晚饭
不行。
- I'm wearing it to dinner.
- No, you're not!
给你
Here you go.
怎么样？
How'd it go?
我想他可能会写一篇正面的文章
Oh, I think he may write a positive article.
噢，一个无神论者
Ooh, a non-skeptic.
那会是个可喜的改变。
That's a pleasant change.
嗯
Yeah.
不要再责备你自己了。
Stop blaming yourself.
没加糖吗？
No sugar.
我马上回来
Be right back.
别闹了，Nancy
Not funny, Nancy.
什么？
What?
别拽我的脚
Stop grabbing my foot.
我什么都没做。
Shut up, I didn't do anything.
嗯～
Yeah, right.
也别再放屁了
And stop farting.
臭死人了
It really stinks.
明明是你放的屁，别什么都怪在我头上，Pew.
Don't blame that on me. It's you. Pew.
爸爸
Dad?
Andrea，为什么你要起床？
Andrea, what are you doing out of bed?
那是什么声音
What's that sound?
那是Cindy，她在我房间，她又梦游了。
It's Cindy. She's in my room.
She's sleepwalking again.
我以前从未见过她这样
I've never seen her do this before.
我记得你说过如果她梦游的时候不要叫醒她。
I remembered you saying not
to wake her if she's like this.
不要，我们把她抱回床上就好
No, we just put her back to bed.
嗨，宝贝～
Hey, hey. Sweetie. Shh.
我们回床上去吧
Let's go back to bed.
她没事了，晚安。
She's okay. Good night.
晚安
Night.
她有梦游了?
她已经有一阵子不这样了
She's sleepwalking again?
She hasn't done that for awhile.
她又去了Andrea的房间
我想Andrea可能被吓到了。
She ended up in Andrea's room too.
I think kind of freaked her out.
那很糟糕，我们应该怎么办
我不知道
- That's not good. What are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
宝贝，你这里又有其他的伤痕了
是吗？
- Honey, you got another bruise here.
- Hmm?
痛不痛?
Does that hurt?
太怪异了
That's weird.
是啊，你可不可以去找个医生看看?
I don't know. Will you do me a favor,
go see a doctor for that?
嗯，我会的。小心开车。
好的
- Yeah, I will. Drive safe.
- Yeah.
我爱你
我也爱你
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Bye!
爱你
Love you!
Cindy，你吃过午饭了吗？
吃过了
- Cindy, you have your lunch?
- Yeah.
是的
Yes, I do.
我好想Sadie呀
I miss Sadie a lot.
她是我最好的朋友
She was my best friend.
你也是我的朋友，对吗？
You're my friend, right?
我们来玩吧
Yeah, let's play.
你在跟谁说话？
Rory.
- Who are you talking to?
- Rory.
Rory？
Rory?
他是我的新朋友
噢，是吗？
- He's my new friend.
- Oh, really?
嗯哼，你想要见见他吗？
当然，可是要怎么见？
- Yeah, do you want to see him?
- Yeah. Uh-huh. How?
用这个
With this.
音乐停止的时候你就会从镜子里看到他站在你的身后
When the music stops, you see him
in the mirror standing behind you.
好
Okay.
但是你必须要拧钥匙
But you have to twist the key.
好
Okay.
妈妈，哈哈
喔～
- Boo, Mommy! Ha-ha!
- Oh!
April，你吓得我心脏病都快发作了
哈哈，骗到你了
- April, you just gave me a heart attack.
- Got you!
好吧，我猜Rory可能不想看到我，是吗？
Well, okay, I guess Rory
doesn't want to see me, huh?
嗯嗯
Hmm. Oh, well.
我们可以玩躲猫猫？
Can we play hide-and-clap?
躲猫猫？
噢～宝贝，我不太想玩
Hide-and-cla--?
Oh, honey, I don't want to play.
求你了妈妈，从来没有人让我玩儿
好吧好吧
- Please! Nobody ever lets me play.
- Okay, okay.
你要记得让我拍三次手。
Remember, you get to ask me
for three claps.
好
Okay.
1，2，3
One, two, three.
我要找地方藏起来了
好
- I'm gonna go hide now!
- Okay.
4，5
Four, five...
6，7
...six, seven...
8，9
...eight, nine...
...ten!
第一次拍手
First clap!
噢 糟糕
Ow. Shit.
第二次拍手
Second clap!
April.
我知道你藏在哪儿
Oh, I know where you're hiding.
还要拍一次手
Give me the third clap.
我要抓到你了
I'm gonna get you now.
我可以听到你的呼吸声
I can hear you breathing.
April.
哈哈，你摘掉眼罩了，，，我赢咯。。
Ha, ha. You took your blindfold off. I win!
你都没有提前发出警告，妈妈
我藏在Christine和Nancy的房间里
You weren't even warm, Mom.
I was in Christine and Nancy's room.
我必须要在这里弄一些routes
不然保险的损失就太大了
I gotta have some routes here,
or I'm gonna lose the insurance on the rig.
那差不多占了一半
That's like half of my rate, man.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
好吧，我会的
I'll, uh-- Yeah, I'll take it.
谢谢
Thank you.
什么是route？
哦，是Florida
- What's the route?
- It's, uh, Florida.
明天开始。
It's a week turnaround. I start tomorrow.
我们会解决这个问题
We'll get through this.
嗯
Yeah.
好了，我们去睡觉吧
Come on, let's go to bed.
别闹了Nancy，那没什么好玩的
Stop it, Nancy. It's not funny anymore.
我在努力入睡，请不要再拽我的脚丫子了
I'm trying to sleep,
please stop grabbing my feet.
Nancy
Nancy?
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
Christine
Christine?
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
你看到它了吗？
Do you see it?
看到什么？
See what?
有人在门后面
There's someone behind the door.
什么？
What?
There's someone standing over there.
有人站在那边
我怎么看不见
I don't see anyone.
它在看着我们
It's looking right at us.
Nancy，别！
Nancy, don't! Nancy.
我没闹，你看！
No, no. Look. Look.
你看，这里什么都没有，看到了吗?
Look, there's no one here. See?
又是那个味道
Ugh. It's that smell again.
噢天哪
Oh, my God.
它就站在你身后
It's standing right behind you.
Christine，Christine，Christine
Christine?! Christine! Christine!
门打不开
God, it won't op--
Christine
不要～～
- Christine!
- No! No! No!
发生什么事了？怎么了？
这里有其他的人。
- What's going on? What happened?
- There was someone else in here!
什么？
在哪儿？
- What?
- Where?
在就门那里，在门后面
By the door. It was behind the door.
宝贝，这里什么都没有
没有人在这里
Honey, there's nothing in here.
There's nobody in here.
有其他人在这里
There was someone else in here!
我正在睡觉，突然有人拽我的脚
I was just sleeping, and then
I felt somebody grab my feet.
那时我以为是Nancy
So I thought it was Nancy.
宝贝，我肯定那只是个噩梦而已。
Well, honey, I'm pretty sure
that it was just a bad dream.
不是，它跟我说话了
No! It talked to me!
它说
It said...
它想要我们全家都死。
...that it wants my family dead.
Winston先生
Mr. Winston!
Winston？Winston？
Winston? Winston?
去他后面
Get behind him.
你要去哪里？
Where you off to?
我要去商店买点儿东西
I just gotta run to the store
for a few things.
为什么你还要继续尝试？
你什么意思？
- Why do you even try?
- What? What do you mean?
得了吧，都15年了，你怎么还可能瞒得过我？
In 15 years have you
ever been able to lie to me?
Gordon神父打电话说，他那里有件案子想让我们去调查一下
Father Gordon called. He's got
a case he wants us to look into.
我跟他说我会自己去看看
Lorraine，我是说只有我自己去。
I said I'd go check it out myself.
Lorraine, myself.
我和你一起去
I'm going with you.
我知道你很担心那种事会再次发生
I know you're worried
it's gonna happen again.
是啊，当然了。我很担心。
Yeah, I am. I really am.
我想我们也许是时候该休息一下了，顺便写完那本书。
Maybe it's just time we take a break.
Write that book.
你还记不记得在我们的婚礼上你跟我说过什么？
Do you remember what you said to me
on our wedding night?
我们可以再来一次吗？
"Can we do it again?"
在那之后
After that.
你说上帝让我们在一起是有原因的，对吗?
You said that God brought us together
for a reason. Right?
我很确定它让我们在一起并不是为了让我们一起写本书
I'm pretty sure it's not to write a book.
我去换衣服
I'm gonna get dressed.
我们把那个声音分离出来了
We've isolated the disturbances to the attic.
我想要你听一下这个
I want you to listen for a second.
天那，就是那个
Oh, my God, that's it.
再来一次，Ed
Do it again, Ed.
现在就只是我的重量
因为你把水管里的水排干了
Right now it's just my weight.
But you take the water coming off the pipe...
风从这个破了的窗户里吹进来，进入管道
...combined with the wind coming
through the broken window...
就会导致这些木板会互相碰撞和摩擦
...these boards are gonna expand
and rub against each other.
这些管道都通向暖气片，所以你可以在整个房间里都听到这些声音
You heard it all through the house
because of these pipes leading to the radiator.
你是说，这个房间没问题
So this place isn't haunted?
是的，完全没问题
No, it rarely is.
类似这样的情况通常都会有合理的解释。
Yeah, there's usually always
some kind of rational explanation.
姑娘们，已经过了就寝时间了
Girls, it's way past your bedtime.
那是谁
Who is that?
究竟是谁在下面？
我要把你锁起来
Who's ever down there,
I'm gonna lock you in now!
Aah! Unh.
Aah!
救命
Help!
Andrea，救命～！
Andrea! Help!
嗨～想要玩躲猫猫吗？
Hey, wanna play hide-and-clap?
Aah!
Cindy？
Cindy?
好吧。。。
Okay, now....
好吗？
All right?
听话～过来
All right, come on.
Come on.
过来
There you go.
今晚你可以和我睡在一起，好吗？
Okay, you can just sleep with me tonight,
all right?
来，躺下
There you go.
There.
Andrea？
救命～～
- Andrea?
- Help! Help! Help!
谁在里面？
Andrea！
- Who's in here?
- Andrea!
Andrea，Andrea，
Andrea? Andrea!
在里面
In here!
救命·～爸爸，救命呀。。是Andrea。
Help, Daddy! Help, it's Andrea!
谁在里面？
Andrea。。
- Who's in here?
- Andrea!
出什么事了？
What happened?
有没有人能告诉我究竟发生什么事了？
Somebody, goddamn it,
tell me what's going on here?
我们通常所指的恐惧，是指人们在面对来自鬼怪的威胁时所导致的
Fear is defined as a feeling of agitation
and anxiety caused by the presence...
害怕和焦虑不安的感觉
...or imminence of danger.
无论是鬼魂，或者恶灵
他们都以此为生
Whether it's a ghost, a spirit
or an entity, they all feed on it.
这个是Maurice
Take Maurice here.
一个只受过三年教育的法裔加拿大农夫
A French-Canadian farmer with
no more than a third-grade education...
当他被附身了之后，他可以讲一口流利的拉丁语。
...yet after he was possessed,
spoke some of the best Latin I'd ever heard.
但有时候前好相反
Sometimes backwards.
他曾经被他的父亲性侵过，并且也常常被虐待。
He'd been molested by his father,
who had also tortured him repeatedly.
一个恶灵入侵了他。
A dark spirit made its home in this man.
现在，如果你注视着他的眼睛，你可以看到他的眼睛在流血
Now, if you look into his eyes,
you can see him tearing blood.
And like that...
他的身体上出现了一个倒置的十字
...an upside-down cross started
to appear from within his body.
好了，Drew，你可以打开灯
All right, Drew, you can hit the lights.
Oh.
你有没有亲自驱过魔？
Did you personally perform the exorcism?
没有，我没有得到许可
不过我做过许多辅助工作
No, I'm not authorized.
But I've assisted on many.
驱魔是非常危险的工作
See, an exorcism
can be very dangerous...
不仅仅是针对受害者，而是要针对所有住在房子里的人。
...not only for the victim,
but for anyone in the room.
Maurice究竟做了什么？
他想要杀了他的妻子。。
- What happened to Maurice?
- He tried to kill his wife...
但是子弹却射到了她的胳膊上。然后他开枪自杀了。
...but instead shot her in the arm
and then turned the gun on himself.
Maurice的一生非常糟坎坷，也很短暂
Maurice had a very troubled life
with little to live for...
没有任何一位驱魔人能救他
...and not even an exorcist
could bring him back.
他已经处在恶灵附身的第三个阶段了
Which brings us to the three stages
of demonic activity:
侵扰，胁迫，占有
Infestation, oppression and possession.
现在我们来说说侵扰
Now, infestation:
通常都是低语，脚步声，对其他未知物质的感知
That's the whispering, the footsteps,
the feeling of another presence...
然后会进入第二个阶段：胁迫
...which ultimately grows
into oppression, the second stage.
在这个阶段，那些心理脆弱的人
Now this is where the victim,
and it's usually the one...
往往会成为受害者
...who's the most
psychologically vulnerable...
...is targeted specifically
by an external force.
这些受害者的行为将会不受自己的意愿所控制
Breaks the victim down.
Crushes their will.
一旦处在这种弱势的状态下，就会很容易进入第三个也就是最后的阶段：占有
And, once in a weakened state, leads them
to the third and final stage: possession.
嗨～Ed? Lorraine?
嗯
- Hey, Ed? Lorraine?
- Yeah.
这里有个人想要跟你说句话
There's someone here
that would like to talk to you.
嗨～
谢谢你，Drew.
- Hi.
- Thanks, Drew.
谢谢你
回头见
- Thank you.
- I'll see you later.
你有什么事吗？
How can we help you?
我的房子里发生了一些非常糟糕的事，你们可以过来看一下吗？
There's something horrible happening in
my house. Could you come and take a look?
现在恐怕有点儿太晚了
You know, uh, it's getting kinda late.
我们真的需要回家了
你不明白。。
- We really need to head to our family.
- You don't understand.
我们理解你的心情，不过，你所说的事通常都会有合理的解释
But we do. There's usually some
sort of rational explanation--
我的五个女儿现在都害怕得要死
我很担心那个东西会伤害我们
I have five daughters who are scared to death.
I'm so afraid this thing wants to hurt us.
你们也有女儿，难道你们不会想尽一切办法来保护你们的女儿？
You have a daughter. Wouldn't you do
anything you could to protect her? Please.
求你了～就过来看一下
Please can you come and take a look?
好吧，我们会去。
Of course we will.
我们会的
快点Jan，快点打开
Come on, Jan! Open up!
Jan，出什么事了？
Jan, what happened?
你的头顶变成黑色了
The top of your head turned black.
你们都站起来，整理一下
You guys straighten up? Thanks.
别傻了，那是假发
Don't be silly, it's a wig.
你好
- Hello. Hi.
- Hi. Hi.
谢谢你们能过来
Thanks for coming.
嗨，我是Roger
我是Lorraine
- Hi, I'm Roger.
- Lorraine.
很高兴见到你，Roger.我是 Ed Warren.
Hey, nice to meet you, Roger. Ed Warren.
谢谢，快请进
- Thanks for coming.
- Please, come in.
谢谢
Thank you.
那么。。
So....
噢，这些漂亮的女孩子们是谁呀？
Oh, my God. Look at you all.
Who are these beautiful young women?
这是 Andrea, 她最大。Nancy, Cindy, Christine...
This is Andrea, the oldest,
Nancy, Cindy, Christine...
这位是April
...and April.
这两位是Warren先生和夫人
It's Mr. and Mrs. Warren.
我们现在都睡在这里
嗯
- We're all sleeping down here now.
- Mm.
女孩们觉得安全一点，也比较暖和。
The girls feel safer and it's warmer.
我总是开着暖气，可是这个房子里总是那么冷
I'm constantly turning up the heat,
but the house is always freezing.
不过那不是火炉的问题
It's not a problem with the furnace.
我是说，我不知道是什么原因
I mean, not that I can find.
过去的几个晚上，这里发生了太多糟糕的事情
It's gotten a lot worse the past few nights.
这里有一股很难闻的味道，就像腐烂的肉一样，整个房子里都是这股味儿
There's this awful smell, like rotting meat.
It moves around the house.
Uh....
怎么了？那是什么？
What? What is it?
腐肉的味道可能意味着有某种恶灵在这里出没
Well, rancid smells could indicate
some type of demonic activity.
噢，天哪
Oh, my God.
那是为了晚上的时候防止那些撞门的声音
That's to keep those doors
from banging at night.
整个晚上都像这样，
Otherwise, it's like:
All night long, just like that.
一次敲三下？
对
- Does it come in threes?
- Yeah.
黎明的时候就会停止？
It stops at dawn?
对
Uh-huh.
有时候那可能意味着是对三位一体的一种侮辱。
Well, sometimes it's meant
as an insult to the Trinity:
所谓的三位一体，就是指基督教里的圣父、圣子及圣灵
The Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
最奇怪的事情是，有很多小鸟
You know, it's the damndest thing,
but we also get all kinds of birds...
总是会飞来撞墙，直到撞断自己的脖子
...that will just fly against the side
of the house and break their necks.
真的吗？
Hm. Really?
还有，房间里的钟表总是会停在凌晨3：07
And the clocks stop at 3:07 a.m.
所有的钟表？
是的
- All of them?
- Every one.
我们本来把那些照片挂在楼梯边的墙壁上
Oh, we were hanging those
along the stairs.
但是总是有什么东西会把它们弄下来，所以就没有再挂了
Something just kept knocking them down,
so we stopped hanging them up.
那就是我想要说到的
That's what I was talking about.
我们刚刚搬进来的时候
It was here when we moved in.
这里有一个地窖，堆满了各种东西。
There's also a lot of stuff in the cellar.
带我去那个地窖
Show me the cellar.
看看她让我干了什么
Look what she made me do.
你正在接收那些信息，对吗宝贝？
You picking up anything in here, hon?
这里曾经发生过很糟糕的事情，Ed
Something awful happened here, Ed.
那些擦伤，也是来这里以后发生的吗？
Those bruises, they from something
that happened here?
噢，那个嘛～我有点贫血。
Oh, it's some iron deficiency thing I have.
既然发生了这么多事，为什么你们不从这里搬出去
You know, with all that's been going on,
why haven't you just moved out?
我不知道应该去哪里
I don't know where
we'd move to, you know?
我们用所有的钱买了这所房子，另外也已经做了各种修理
We got all our money tied up in this place
and had a lot of repairs on top of that.
我也不知道有谁会让我们这么一大家子暂住。
And I don't know anybody whose gonna
take in a family of seven indefinitely.
这也就是为什么我们会去找你们。
That's why we tracked you down.
我们很高兴你们找到我们
We're glad you found us.
我们开始吧
All right, let's get started.
我是Ed Warren，现在是1971年11月1号
My name is Ed Warren.
It's November 1st, 1971.
我和Carolyn Perron坐在这里
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron...
她和她的家人最近正在经历一些超自然的事件。
...who, with her family, has been
experiencing supernatural occurrences.
你来说
Okay, go ahead.
我们从哪里开始？
Where do I start?
从最初的发生的事情开始
From the first occurrence.
我猜应该是从那些钟表开始
I guess it was the clocks.
妈妈和爸爸告诉我，你有一个朋友
Mom and Dad tell me
that you have a friend.
他的名字叫Rory，他也住在这里。
His name's Rory.
He lives here too.
噢。
可是他总是很悲伤
- Hmm.
- But he's always sad.
为什么？
Why is that?
他不要告诉我，可是我觉得他可能遇到过不好的事。
He won't tell me but I think
something bad happened to him.
你介不介意我见见Rory？
Do you mind if I try to see Rory?
嗨～
Hey.
怎么了？
What is it?
这座房子是我们从拍卖会上买的，所以我们也不晓得以前住在这里的是谁。
We bought it at auction from the bank, so,
you know, we never knew who lived here.
Lorraine和我都觉得你们的房子需要清洁。
Well, Lorraine and I both feel that
what your house needs is a cleansing.
我是说，需要驱魔
An exorcism.
什么？驱魔？
What, exorcism?
我以为需要驱魔的是人，而不是房子
I thought that was something
that you do to people.
不，那不一定。
No, not necessarily, no.
我们必须要离开这里
We have to get out of here.
恐怕那已经没有用了
I'm afraid that's not gonna help.
Lorraine看见了一些东西
Lorraine saw something, which--
你来告诉他们，宝贝
Go ahead, hon.
我一直能看到有黑色的东西在你们的房子里出没
I've been seeing the dark entity
that haunts your house...
还有房子外面
...and your land.
我刚刚进门的时候就看到它了
I saw it first when I came
through your door.
在你们的身后
It was latched to your back.
后来我又在客厅里看到它，和那些女孩子们在一起
And then I saw it again with the girls
when we walked into the living room.
无论你们去哪里
And it doesn't matter where you go...
那个黑死的东西都会附着在你的家人身上
...this dark entity has latched itself
to your family...
它的存在完全是依靠你们
...and it's feeding off you.
即使我们离开这里？
Even if we leave?
有时候，当你们被附身以后，就好象踩在口香糖上
Sometimes when you get haunted,
it's like stepping on gum.
你走到哪里，它们就会跟到哪里
You take it with you.
听着，我必须要告诉你
这里有很多恶灵
Look, I gotta tell you,
you have a lot of spirits in here...
但是有一个让我很担心，它非常可怕
...but this is the one that I'm most
worried about, because it is so hateful.
好吧，那我们该怎么办？
我们可以请一个神父吗？
Okay, so what do we do?
Can we call a priest?
要是那么容易就好了
I wish it were that easy.
驱魔是一项很古老的仪式，需要经过很多年的练习。
Performing an exorcism is an archaic
procedure. Requires years of training.
即便如此，还是会出错
And even then,
I have seen it go horribly wrong.
而且，在那之前，首先要得到教会的批准
But before we even get that far,
the church has to authorize it first.
那就意味着我们必须要先调查和研究，收集证据并且能证明这里的确存在恶灵
It means we gotta investigate,
gather evidence and provide proof...
那是最难的部分
...and that's the hard part.
你们的孩子们有没有受洗？
Have your children been baptized?
没有，我们一直没有来得及做那个，实际上我们也不算是虔诚的教会家庭。
Uh, no, we never got around to that.
We're not really a churchgoing family.
你们可能需要重新考虑一下，我们出现在这里只会让事情变得更糟糕/
Well, you may want to rethink that.
Our presence here could make things worse.
为什么?
Why?
因为对他们来说，我们是个威胁
Because we're a threat.
但是你们不一样，无论你们做什么，都不会像我们一样。
And whatever you're dealing with here
isn't gonna like us.
到目前为止它没有做过任何暴力的事情，那是个很好的预兆
So far it hasn't done anything violent,
and that's a good sign.
我们会让我们的人去查一下这座房子的来源
So we're gonna have our guy
do some homework on the property...
看看我们面对的究竟是什么东东
...to see what we're up against.
Judy，你在做什么?
Judy, what are you up to?
我给你带了件礼物
- I got you a present.
- Aah.
我和Nanna去教堂院子里的售卖会了
Me and Nanna got these
at the church's yard sale.
宝贝
一个给你，一个给我
- Honey.
- One for you and one for me.
哇哦
她放了一张你和爸爸的照片在我的项链里
- Aw.
- She put a picture...
...of you and Daddy in mine.
Nanna说这样一来我们就会永远在一起了
Nanna said this way
we'll always be together.
你会和我在一起，我会和你在一。
You'll be with me and I'll be with you.
我很想你和爸爸
I miss you and Daddy.
嘿～宝贝
Hey, hon.
嗯？
Yup.
你肯定不会相信，Carolyn的声音没有被录进去。
You're not gonna believe this.
Carolyn's voice didn't record.
你说什么？
What do you mean?
你听
Listen.
我是Ed Warren，现在是1971年11月1日
My name is Ed Warren.
It's November 1st, 1971.
我和Carolyn Perron坐在这里
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron...
她和她的家人最近正在经历一些超自然的事件。
...who, with her family, has been
experiencing supernatural occurrences.
你说吧
Okay, go ahead.
从开始讲
From the first occurrence.
你听，什么都没有
Nothing.
全都没有
The whole time.
我不知道，你发现什么了吗？
太多了
- I don't know. You find anything?
- Lots.
我是说，难怪他们要经历这一切
I mean, it's no wonder they're
going through what they are.
那是最早期的农舍
That's the original farmhouse.
是由一个叫Jedson Sherman的男人建于1863年
It was built in 1863 by a man
named Jedson Sherman...
他娶了一个叫Bathsheba的女人
...who was married to a woman
named Bathsheba.
Ed，Bathsheba和Mary Towne Estye是亲戚
Ed, she's related to Mary Towne Estye.
她是那些在Salem被控告的女巫之一。
She was one of the women
accused of witchcraft in Salem.
她在审讯期间被吊死了
哇哦
- She was hung during the trials.
- Wow.
Bathsheba嫁给Jedson之后，生了一个孩子。
After Bathsheba married Jedson,
they had a baby...
那个孩子7岁的时候
...and when the baby was 7 days old...
Jedson发现她正在壁炉前面用她的孩子献祭。
...Jedson caught her sacrificing it
in front of the fireplace.
她跑到码头前的那棵树前
She ran out to that tree by the dock...
爬上树，宣告她热爱撒旦
...climbed up, proclaimed her love
to Satan...
并且诅咒任何想要拿走她的土地的人，然后上吊死了。
...cursed anyone who tried
to take her land, and hung herself.
她死亡的时间正好是凌晨3：07
Time of death was pronounced at 3:07
in the morning.
噢，那可以解释一些事。
Well, that explains a few things.
嗯，这个也是。
Yeah, so does this.
她最后的名字是Walker，30年代的时候她住在那里
Her last name's Walker.
She lived there in the '30s.
她有个孩子名字叫Rory，他在树林里神秘地消失了
She had a boy named Rory who
mysteriously disappeared in the woods.
在那之后，她在地窖里自杀了。
Then she killed herself in the cellar.
那还不是全部
And that's not all.
从那之后，这座200亩土地就被分块，廉价出售了
So, what was the original 200-acre farm
has since been subdivided and sold off.
这里还有另外一个男孩子在池塘里淹死了。他住在旁边的房子里
There was another boy who drowned in
a pond here. He lived in a house over here.
还有一位女仆，也在隔壁的房子里自杀了。
And a woman who worked as a maid in a
neighboring home, she committed suicide too.
无论是谁得到她的土地
People who took her land.
我和Carolyn Perron坐在这里
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron...
她和她的家人最近正在经历一些超自然的事件。
...who, with her family, has been
experiencing supernatural occurrences.
你来
Okay, go ahead.
从头说
From the first occurrence.
Brad来了
Here's Brad.
没问题吧？
嗯
- You find it okay?
- Oh, yeah.
Drew，这位是Brad警官
Drew, this is Officer Brad.
警官 Brad Hamilton
Harrisville, Rhode Island P.D.
Officer Brad Hamilton,
很高兴见到你
Hm. Nice to meet you, man.
你是那位运气超好的新警察？
我猜是吧
- So you're the lucky new cop, huh?
- Guess so.
你知道你不可能射中鬼魂，对吗？
有好一点儿，Drew
- You know you can't shoot ghosts, right?
- Take it easy on him, Drew.
大家过来帮我把这些东东卸下来
All right, guys,
help me get this stuff unloaded.
你拿这个
You take this.
嗨 Roger
Hi, Roger.
Drew你把这里弄完之后，就到楼上去。
All right. When you're finished here,
why don't you hit upstairs, all right, Drew?
没问题吧
You got it.
那辆雪佛来怎么了？
What's wrong with the Chevy?
坏了
Ugh, what's not wrong with her?
需要一个新的换油器
噢，是吗
- Needs a new carburetor to start.
- Oh, yeah?
先扔着吧，过一段时间再修理
Kind of put fixing her up
on hold for a while.
Yeah. Ahem.
Brad，麻烦递给我一个调温器。
Hey, Brad, hand me a thermostat,
would you?
这是什么东东？
What's this, uh, do?
如果温度急剧下降
When there's an instant drop
in temperature...
调温器可以触动相机的快门
...the thermostat
triggers the camera to take a picture.
你真的有拍摄到那些东西吗？
You've actually caught things on film?
嗯，当然
Well, yeah, that's, uh, the point.
为什么我们要在外边
Why, uh--? Why out here?
这里是女巫下咒的地方
Well, this is where the witch
committed suicide.
她就在站的那个地方上方的树杈上上吊死了
She hung herself from that branch
right above where you're standing.
多狠毒的妈妈才会把自己的孩子杀了
How could a mother kill her own child?
对她来说，那并不是她的孩子
It was never a child to her.
她只是在利用上帝赐给她的礼物来对抗圣灵
She just used her God-given gift
as the ultimate offense against him.
女巫们认为那会提高她们在撒旦眼中的地位
Witches believe it elevates their status
in the eyes of Satan.
噢
Mm.
哇哦，你们在海边的那天真是个美好的日子呀
Wow.
That's a nice day at the beach, huh?
你是怎么知道的？
How did you know?
这就是所谓的洞察力。就像掀开窗帘的一角去偷窥别人的生活一样。
It's an insight. It's like a peek through
the curtain into another person's life.
嗯
Mm.
对我来说，那是非常重要的一天。我们沿着海岸开了很久的车
That day meant so much to me.
We were driving along the coast.
Nancy说那里的风景好美
Nancy pointed out
how pretty the view was.
我觉得应该拍张家庭合影。
I thought this is a perfect opportunity
for a photo.
我们就要开始新的生活了。新的房子，新的开始。
We're gonna start fresh, you know?
A new house, a new beginning.
我从未见过Roger和女孩们那么地开心
You should have seen Roger and the girls.
I've never seen them so happy.
干杯～！
Cheese!
对我而言她们就是我的全部。
They mean the world to me.
把你的手放在桌子上
Put your hand flat on the desk.
拿开
Yeah, and take it off.
我们来看看
Here we go.
看到了吗
See?
它可以让我们看到一些我们平时看不到的东西
It just reveals to us what
the naked eye can't see.
非常先进，对吗
Pretty far out, isn't it?
对，很好玩
Yeah, it's groovy.
Drew， 你把Bolex准备好了吗？
Drew, you got the Bolex ready for Brad?
嗯，弄好了
Yeah, already locked and loaded, sir.
怎么了？我憋不住了
What? I had to go.
所有的房间都安装好了
All the rooms are coming in pretty good.
很好
Good.
瓶子里是什么？
What's in the bottle?
圣水
Holy water.
放一些宗教的标识
Presence of religious icons...
会刺激那些邪恶的东西
from anything unholy.
可以激怒它们
Sort of pisses them off.
我要把这些标识多放几个地方，看看会发生什么
So I set these throughout the house,
see if I can stir things up a bit.
就像在魔鬼面前拿着十字架？
太对了
- Like holding a cross to a vampire?
- Yeah. Exactly.
除了吸血鬼以外
Except I don't believe in vampires.
那不是我
Wasn't me.
Brad，拿着相机
Brad, get the camera.
好
Okay.
现在是9:18，我们正在去地窖，
All right, it's 9:18, we're headed down into the
cellar where the door's just opened on its own.
我和Lorraine、Brad Hamilton警官在一起
I have Lorraine and Officer Brad Hamilton
with me.
我们要关掉地窖的灯
Let's keep the cellar light off.
如果你想要和我们联系，就发个信号
Give us a sign that you wanna
communicate with us.
宝贝，你没事吧
Hon, you all right?
这里绝对有东西
There's definitely something here.
关上门，弄点儿动静出来
我的手好冷
- All right, close the door. Move something.
- My hands are so cold.
快点
Come on.
不
No.
它跑了。。
It's gone. It's gone.
什么都没有
I got nothing.
好吧
Okay.
就像我说过的，不一定总会成功。
Well, like I said, it doesn't always work
when you want it to.
也许相机会拍到点有用的东东
Yeah, maybe the camera picked
something up.
小心点儿
Watch out!
对于一个不相信这些东东的人而言
For a guy who doesn't believe...
那扇门撞上的时候你好象真有点儿吓着了
...you looked a little freaked out
when that door slammed shut.
那肯定是个draft（不知咋翻译）
It must have been a draft.
噢，那很好笑
Oh, that's funny.
A draft never put that look
on my face before.
我相信那个钟表
I believe the clock.
现在是3:08
It's 3:08.
让我看看你的眼镜
Let me see your glasses.
这是给你的
For you.
我想待会儿我可能会带几个女孩子去吃冰淇淋,你觉得怎么样?
I think I might take some girls for ice cream
later on. What do you say about that?
太好了
宝贝,你想要一起来吗
- Yeah!
- Honey, you wanna come?
不,我快累死了,我只想休息一下.
I'm exhausted. I'm just gonna take a nap.
The late nights are getting to me.
那是个好主意.你去休息吧
That's probably a good idea.
Why don't you get some rest.
Lorraine和我会照看这里
真的吗
- Lorraine and I'll watch over things for a bit.
- Really?
我先走了,一个小时之后就该轮到我值班了.
I'm gonna take off.
I have a shift starting in an hour.
这个房间里已经很久没有像今天这样热闹了
The house hasn't felt like this
in a long time.
我想有你们在这里,孩子们会觉得非常安全.
I think the kids feel a lot safer
with you around.
我可以习惯这个
什么?我洗衣服?
- I could get used to this.
- What, me doing laundry?
哈哈
真讨厌
- Ha-ha-ha.
- You're funny.
不是,我是说这个地方
No, this place.
很不错的地方,空气也很新鲜
Nice, fresh country air.
他们的家庭也非常美好
They have such a beautiful family,
don't they?
嗯,最小的那个,April,你有没有看到她那给我煎饼?
Yeah, that little one, April,
did you see her bring me pancakes?
我们必须要帮助他们
We've gotta help them.
我知道
I know.
我会从那个雪佛莱开始
- I'll start with the Chevy.
- Heh.
Carolyn
Carolyn!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
Carolyn,开门
Carolyn, open the door.
Carolyn,快开门
Carolyn, open up!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我没事
你是不是生病了
- Oh, I'm fine.
- Are you sick?
我醒来后觉得好恶心,再没什么事
我觉得我好像看到...
- I woke up feeling nauseous, that's all.
- I thought I saw--
我听到Roger和女孩们
I hear Roger and the girls.
等一下
One minute.
大家想要玩游戏们?
无聊
- Guys, do you wanna play a game?
- Boring!
谢谢你爸爸
Thank you, Daddy.
我们进去吧
Let's go inside.
我以为那是你
I thought that was you.
希望你不要介意
Hey, I hope you don't mind.
我有个好主意.
I got a good deal on a rebuild
at that wrecking yard in Smithfield.
你看起来好像知道你在做什么
嗯,等着瞧
- No, you look like you know what you're doing.
- Yeah, we'll see.
Roger,这个地方真不错
Got a nice place here, Roger.
Lorraine和我一直想要这样的地方
Lorraine and I always wanted
a spot in the country.
我会把这个卖给你
I'll sell you this one.
把扳手递给我
Hey, hand me a wrench, would you?
你待在这里对我们来说真的意味着很多
Hey, uh, it really means a lot
to us to have you here.
我必须要承认,我有点儿害怕进去那里
I gotta admit, I was a little
bit skeptical going in.
只是想要谢谢你
Just wanna say thank you, though,
for coming out when you did.
其实都是Lorraine的主意
I can't take the credit.
That's, uh-- That's all Lorraine.
那时我并不想来
为什么?
- I didn't want to.
- Oh. Why's that?
Lorraine看到的,感觉到的,接触过的,都可以帮助别人.
Whatever Lorraine sees, feels, touches,
it helps people.
但是她也因此受到了伤害
But it also takes a toll on her.
每次一点点
Little piece each time.
几个月之前,我们正在处理一个案子
Couple months ago
we were working on a case.
她看见了某种东西
She saw something.
那次她受到了很大的伤害
It took a real big piece.
我们回到家以后
When we got home...
她把自己锁进房子里
...she went into our room,
locked herself in...
不说话,不吃东西,整整8天都没有出门
...didn't talk, didn't eat,
didn't come out for eight days.
她看到了什么
What'd she see?
走开
Get out of here!
我不知道
I don't know.
我也没有问
And I won't ask.
我去找点儿吃的,你想要点儿吗
I need to reload. You want some?
我不要,谢谢
I'm good, thanks.
好吧
All right.
看看她让我都干了些什么
Look what she made me do.
Hey.
Ed?
看看她让我都干了些什么
Look what she made me do!
Ed!
兄弟,你没事吧
Dude, you okay?
坚持住,Brad,发生什么事了
Hold up, Brad. What's going on?
我看到了一个女人,打扮得像个女仆
I saw someone. There was
a woman dressed as a maid.
Ed,有动静了
Ed? Ed, we're getting something.
那是Cindy,她在梦游
等等,我们需要这个
- It's just Cindy. She's sleepwalking.
- No, wait. We need this.
为什么我们要拍Cindy的照片
Why do we need pictures of Cindy?
她没有碰到机关
She didn't trigger it.
你什么意思?
有人和她在一起
- What do you mean she didn't trigger it?
- Somebody's with her.
谁?
Who?
Cindy!
过来这里,这里很安全
Hey, over here. It's safe.
那里有其他人和她在一起
There's someone else in there with her.
我听到别人的声音,你听~~
I'm hearing another voice. Here, listen.
跟着我,来这边
Follow me. This way.
我就藏在这里
This is where I hide.
Cindy!
Cindy?
她要去哪里?
Where'd she go, Ed?
窗户是锁着的
Windows are locked.
Ed,她去了哪里?
Ed, where'd she go?
Brad,打开紫外线灯
Brad, get the UV light.
什么?
问Drew.
- The what?
- Just ask Drew.
Drew,我需要紫外线灯
- Drew, I need a UV light.
- Uh--
在这边来
Here, that's it. Go, go, go, go!
关掉灯
Turn off the light.
让开点
Get out of the way.
好
Okay.
拿着灯
Hit the lights!
找到她了
Found her.
Here we go.
抱好她
是的
- All right. You got her?
- Yeah.
Rory害怕的时候他就藏在这里
That's where Rory hides
when he's afraid.
宝贝,把April的音乐盒递给我一下
Hon? Could I have April's
music box, please?
Cindy怎么样?
她什么都不记得了
- How's Cindy?
- She doesn't remember a thing.
来,接着
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
Lorraine!
不
No.
Lorraine!
是她让我做的
She made me do it.
Ed!
Lorraine!
Come on! Lorraine!
Ed!
Ed!我知道她做了什么
Ed, I know what she did.
我抓到你了,我知道,没事
我知道她做了什么
- I got you. I know. It's okay.
- I know what she did.
我知道她做了什么.她迫使那些母亲杀死了孩子们
I know what she did. She possessed
the mother to kill the child.
她每天晚上都来找Carolyn
She visits Carolyn every night.
这就是那些伤痕的来源
That's what the bruise marks are!
She's feeding off of her!
Uh....
Nancy?
Nancy!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
Nancy?
Nancy!
抓住她
Grab her!
爸爸,救命
Daddy! Help!
Nancy?
Nancy!
她没事吧?
Is she okay?
没事了
It's okay, I got you.
你拍到那些了吗
Did you get that?
拍到了
Yeah.
我要把那些照片冲洗出来,带去给Gordon神父看
I'll have the footage developed
and get it over to Father Gordon.
他是我们在教堂的联络人,我想我们很快就会收到回复.
He's our liaison at the church.
I imagine we'll get a pretty fast response.
听着Roger
嗯?
- Listen, Roger?
- Yeah?
听着,我找到那些驱魔师会马上就回来,但是Lorraine
Listen, when we get the exorcist,
I'll be back. But Lorraine--
我明白
在Drew注意到你之前都要照顾好她
- Yeah, I understand.
- Until then Drew's gonna keep an eye on you.
Ed,谢谢你所做的一切
- Hey, Ed, thank you for everything.
- Yeah.
Mommy?
That's everything.
Judy?
天哪
Oh, God!
Judy
Judy?
Lorraine,等等
Lorraine! Wait!
等一下,怎么了?
Lorraine. What?
妈妈,是我,Judy还好吗?
Mom, it's me. Is Judy okay?
什么?您能再去看一下吗
- What?
- Can you go check, please?
妈妈,就去看一下
Damn it, Mom, just check, please!
告诉我究竟发生什么事了
是Judy
- Are you gonna tell me what's going on?
- It's Judy.
什么?你是什么意思?
What? What do you mean?
什么?
What?
谢谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
对不起妈妈.我不是故意要吓你的,晚一点我会解释的.好吗
Mom, I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to scare you. I'll explain later, okay?
发生什么事情了
What the hell happened?
我刚刚看到Judy在水里
I had a vision of Judy in the water.
我知道那是某种警告
I know it was some kind of warning.
我知道
I know it.
好吧
Okay.
走吧,我们离开这里
Let's get out of here.
然后呢?
你开玩笑的吧?
- So?
- Yeah, well, you weren't kidding.
没有
No.
听着Ed,这说起来有点儿复杂,因为那些孩子没有受过洗
Look, Ed, this is complicated
because the kids aren't baptized.
我明白
而且,这个家庭也不是我们教堂的成员
- No, I understand.
- And the family are not members of the church.
别说那个
- Oh, come on.
- And....
尤其是,这要得到罗马教会的直接批准
The approval would have to come
directly from the Vatican.
神父,我们从来没有见过这样的事
Father, we've never seen nothing like this.
是啊,我也没有
Yeah, well, neither have l.
神父,他们没有太多时间了
Father, they don't have a lot of time.
好吧
All right.
我会亲自督促这事儿.成吗?
I'll push it through myself.
谢谢你神父
谢谢你
- Thank you, Father. Thank you.
- Thank you.
我们等你电话
- All right, we'll wait for your call.
- Yeah.
妈妈,爸爸
Mommy? Daddy?
妈妈
Mommy?
爸爸
Daddy?
Dad?
奶奶
Nanna?
Aah!
奶奶
Nanna!
奶奶,救命
Nanna, help! Nanna, help!
Judy?
奶奶
Nanna!
救命
Help!
奶奶
- Nanna!
Judy?,快开门
妈妈
- Judy, open the door!
- Mom!
Ed,这里有点儿不对劲
什么?
- Ed, there's something wrong.
- What?
奶奶
Nanna!
- Judy!
救命
- Help!
- Judy!- Judy!快开门
怎么了?
- Judy! Judy, open this door!
- What is it?
她出什么事了?- Judy!
- What's wrong with her? Judy!
躲开~~
- Hey, move. Move, move, move, move.
Judy, 退后
Judy, get back, honey. Get back!
快点儿
- Come on!
- Hurry.
救命
Help! Help!
离们远一点,Judy,
Get away from the door, Judy!
Aah!
天哪,你还好吗
Oh, God! Are you okay?
有人拿着Annabelle玩偶坐在椅子里
There was someone rocking
in the chair with Annabelle.
什么
What?
没事了
It's okay.
她仍然很害怕
She's still in the case.
没事了
It's okay.
没事了～～
It's okay. It's okay.
爸爸～～
- Dad! Dad!
- Daddy!
爸爸～妈妈刚刚和Christine、 April一起离开了
Dad! Dad! Mom just left
with Christine and April.
我什么都没说，直接开车就走了。我不知道发生什么事了
She went in the car and drove away.
I don't know what happened.
她的身上全是腐肉的味道。
她也没有说除了上面事
- She smells like rotting meat.
- She didn't say what was going on.
什么？她走了？去哪儿了
走了，我不知道她去了哪里
- What do you mean, she left? Left where?
- Gone! I don't know where she was going.
妈妈～我们要去哪里？
Where are we going, Mom?
你好，我是Roger
- Hello?
- It's Roger.
Carolyn出事了
Something's going on with Carolyn.
Andrea说她带着Christine 和 April走了
Andrea was here,
said Carolyn took off with Christine and April.
女孩们说她的味道闻起来怪极了。。
胁迫母亲。。。。
- The girls said she smelled like rotten meat.
- Possesses the mother...
杀害自己的孩子。。她会把女孩们带回家去
...to kill the child, that's what she does.
She's taking them to the house.
Roger，马上回家。我们在那里碰面
Roger, get back to the house now.
I'll meet you.
锁上们，拉上窗帘。离电话远点儿
Lock the door, close the blinds.
Stay off the phone!
快去
Go.
我和你一起去
不行，你和Judy待在一起
- I'm coming.
- No, you stay with Judy.
保护Judy的唯一办法就是让这个破事儿早点结束
Only way to protect Judy
is if we stop this where it started.
否则，它会再次骚扰我们
这就是我的目的。
- Otherwise, she'll latch onto us again.
- That's exactly why I am going.
我不能让你一个人去面对那个女巫。
You think I'm gonna let you walk
into this alone?
我不能没有你。
I can't lose you.
你不会失去我。
You won't.
我们一起去，让这一切都结束吧。
Let's finish this together.
门锁着
Carolyn!
- Agh! It's locked.
- Carolyn!
Roger!
走开
Get out of the way!
Roger!
- Ed!
- Roger!
- Carolyn!
- Ed!
我们下来了
- We're down here!
Carolyn,不要～～
Carolyn, don't!
No, no! She's got--!
抓着她的手，拿剪刀来
Get her hand! Get the scissors!
我们要把她弄到车里去
带她去哪里？
- We gotta get her to the car!
- And bring her where?
去找牧师
To take her to the priest
for the exorcism.
April在哪儿
April
- Where's April?
- April?
April
April!
把Christine带去车子里，找到April
Take Christine to the car and find April!
April
April!
快点
Come on!
她不会让Carolyn离开这座房间
你说什么？
- She won't let her leave the house.
- What do you mean?
她一旦离开这所房子，女巫就会杀死她
- If we take her out, the witch will kill her.
- Agh!
Roger!
Carolyn!
快
Go!
Carolyn!
Carolyn?
先把你房子这里
Okay, I'm gonna put you in here.
Come on.
进去，待在车子里
我不想一个人待在这里
- Get in. Stay in here.
- I don't wanna stay here by myself.
不管发生什么事，都要待在这里。我很快回来
Stay in here no matter what.
I'll be back.
我必须要找到April，好吗？我很快就回来，我保证
I have to find April, okay?
I'll be back, I promise.
April?
你还好吗？
You okay?
不要～
Stop!
Brad!
Brad! Brad!
Aah!
找个东西把她绑起来
Let's get something to tie her up!
拽着点儿
Hold it.
我要打电话给Gordon神父，他必须要过来这里
I gotta call Father Gordon.
We gotta get him out here.
他离这里太远了。
看看她，，我想她已经坚持不住了。
He's too far away.
She won't make it. Look at her.
那么你必须要离开
你在说什么？
- Then you need to leave.
- What are you talking about?
我必须要开始驱魔
I have to do it. The exorcism.
什么？我以为你说我们需要一个神父，你又不是神父
What? I thought you said we
need a priest. You're not a priest.
你难道还有更好的主意？
他可以做到。
- Well, you got a better idea?
- He can do it.
你可以做到
但是你必须要离开这里
- You can do it.
- But you gotta get out of here.
我不会离开你
如果你待在这里，我是不会做这种事儿的。
- I'm not leaving you!
- Damn it, I'm not doing this with you in here!
上帝让我们在一起，是有原因的。
这个就是原因
God brought us together for a reason.
This is it.
我去拿书
I'm gonna get the book.
April!
以圣父、圣子以及圣灵的名义
"In the name of the Father,
the Son, the Holy Spirit."
April!
抓好
Hold her still! Hold her still!
过来这边，把她抓好了
Come here! Hold her still!
April!
April?
April，你在下面吗？
April, you under there?
April!
Carolyn，Carolyn，不要屈服！不要让她带走你
Carolyn. Carolyn. Don't give in!
Don't let her take you!
Ed!停下来，你会杀死她的。快停止
Ed! You gotta stop,
you're killing her. Stop!
不，他不能停止
No, he can't!
Roger,救救我
Roger, help me!
Ed! 妈的，快停下
Ed! Goddamn it, stop it!
明白了吗，我们在拯救她的灵魂
Understand this! We are
now fighting for her soul!
以耶稣基督、所有的天使和圣人的名义
"In the name of Jesus Christ,
the saints and all the angels...
我命令你，马上停止作恶。。。
...I command you to reveal yourself!"
Roger,
Roger, help me!
放她下来
Put her down!
Carolyn!
Ed,小心
- Ed, look out!
- Unh!
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
抓紧她，别让她起来
Hold her still! Don't let her up!
我们失去她了，Roger!
We're losing her, Roger!
该死的，离我家人远一点，听到了吗
Damn you! You leave my family alone,
you hear me?
我不知道你是个什么东西，但是离我妻子远一点。
I don't know what you are, but you leave
my wife alone, goddamn it!
放开她
听到了吗？放开她
Let her go!
Do you hear me? Let her go!
放开她
Let her go, goddamn it! Let her go!
她已经死了
She's already gone.
现在，你们全部都要死
And now you're all gonna die.
April!
我找到她了。她在厨房下面
I found her! She's under the house!
Under the kitchen!
别
Don't! No!
抓住她
Get her!
这边，
Carolyn!
- Here.
- Carolyn!
Carolyn!
她在那边的洞里。
- Carolyn!
- She's in that hole. Right there.
Carolyn!，天哪，不要～～
Carolyn? Oh, my God. No!
我进不去，够不到她
Can't go in. Can't reach.
不要，Carolyn!不要～～
No! Carolyn, don't!
不要
Carolyn, no!
Bathsheba!
以上帝的力量，我命令你回到地狱吧
By the power of God,
I condemn you back to hell!
这是你的女儿
This is your daughter!
你不能屈服
- You can't give in!
- Agh!
Roger.，我们要让她自己和女巫抗争
to fight from the inside.
不要让她这样做
Don't let her do this.
Don't let this thing do this.
你必须要抗争
你比她强！
You gotta fight it.
You're stronger than she is.
你必须要抗争
Roger!继续
- You gotta fight!
- Keep it going, Roger!
你必须要和我们在一起，好吗？快点回来 Carolyn.
You gotta stay with us, all right?
Come on back, Carolyn.
起作用了。把她带回来
You're in, that's it! Get her back!
记得你给我看过的东西吗？
- Remember what you showed me.
- No!
记不记得你说过你永远不会忘记你们在海边的日子？
Remember that day that you said
you would never forget.
你说他们是你的全世界
You said they meant the world to you.
你要放弃这一切吗
This is what you'll be leaving behind.
妈妈
Mommy?
Oh.
都结束了
It's over.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
我爱你
I love you so much. I love you so much.
我那么爱你
I love you so much.
我很开心
I'm so happy.
你脸上的那是draft弄的？
A draft do that to your face?
以后无论在哪里，我一定要带着一个枪手
I'd take a guy with a gun any day.
你做得很棒
You did good.
不，都是你的功劳
No, you did.
我要打电话给Gordon神父，告诉他这里发生的一切
I'll call Father Gordon
and let him know what happened.
听起来不错
Sounds good.
罗马教廷批准了
The Vatican approved the exorcism.
好消息
Heh. Nice timing.
明天我们可以去见他。
And if we can, then he'd like
to meet with us tomorrow.
长岛有一个案件，他想要跟我们讨论一下。
There's a case in Long Island
he'd like to discuss.
真的吗？
Really?